[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "And how does it all end?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "does", "it", "all", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Well, it all ended with us not getting any gas.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "all", "ended", "with", "us", "not", "getting", "any", "gas", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "How are you seeing it down there on the ground?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "seeing", "it", "down", "there", "on", "the", "ground", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Well, there's a lot of emotion, there's just thousands of volunteers out here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "emotion", ",", "there", "'s", "just", "thousands", "of", "volunteers", "out", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "And as a former commander yourself, how do you think the president's done this week in terms of his role as commander-in-chief in what was really a national crisis?", "question_tokens": ["And", "as", "a", "former", "commander", "yourself", ",", "how", "do", "you", "think", "the", "president", "'s", "done", "this", "week", "in", "terms", "of", "his", "role", "as", "commander-in-chief", "in", "what", "was", "really", "a", "national", "crisis", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "I think he's done extremely well in terms of his sympathy and empathy for the groups, his visit.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "done", "extremely", "well", "in", "terms", "of", "his", "sympathy", "and", "empathy", "for", "the", "groups", ",", "his", "visit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "What did you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "I thought it was a fair appraisal.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "it", "was", "a", "fair", "appraisal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "Were you pleased that the marathon was canceled?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "pleased", "that", "the", "marathon", "was", "canceled", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "When you said that some American lives may have been lost because of incompetence, do you lay the blame squarely at the president's door?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "said", "that", "some", "American", "lives", "may", "have", "been", "lost", "because", "of", "incompetence", ",", "do", "you", "lay", "the", "blame", "squarely", "at", "the", "president", "'s", "door", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Last time I checked, Piers, he's the commander-in- chief.", "answer_tokens": ["Last", "time", "I", "checked", ",", "Piers", ",", "he", "'s", "the", "commander-in-", "chief", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "ORGAN: Do you believe, as some Republicans do, that the White House or certainly people close to the White House were aware of what was happening on that fateful night and decided not to do anything?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Do", "you", "believe", ",", "as", "some", "Republicans", "do", ",", "that", "the", "White", "House", "or", "certainly", "people", "close", "to", "the", "White", "House", "were", "aware", "of", "what", "was", "happening", "on", "that", "fateful", "night", "and", "decided", "not", "to", "do", "anything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "NNS", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "They either were aware of it and decided not to do anything or they were asleep at the switch.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "either", "were", "aware", "of", "it", "and", "decided", "not", "to", "do", "anything", "or", "they", "were", "asleep", "at", "the", "switch", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House", "White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Staten Island"], "TIME": ["this morning"]}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Did you change your opinion when you saw that overnight and this morning, or were you still of the view, you know what, we should get on with it?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "change", "your", "opinion", "when", "you", "saw", "that", "overnight", "and", "this", "morning", ",", "or", "were", "you", "still", "of", "the", "view", ",", "you", "know", "what", ",", "we", "should", "get", "on", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Well, I was in Staten Island this morning, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "in", "Staten", "Island", "this", "morning", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Nevada", "New York"]}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Do you think the president has been an outstanding leader?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "president", "has", "been", "an", "outstanding", "leader", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "I don't know what the heck he was doing in Nevada while people were still being discovered dead in New York.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "the", "heck", "he", "was", "doing", "in", "Nevada", "while", "people", "were", "still", "being", "discovered", "dead", "in", "New", "York", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Oh, I don't go that far at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "go", "that", "far", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "Should he now come to New York, the president?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "he", "now", "come", "to", "New", "York", ",", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "President hasn't been to New York.", "answer_tokens": ["President", "has", "n't", "been", "to", "New", "York", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Ohio"]}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Can Mitt Romney become president realistically if he doesn't win Ohio?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "Mitt", "Romney", "become", "president", "realistically", "if", "he", "does", "n't", "win", "Ohio", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Either one can win without Ohio.", "answer_tokens": ["Either", "one", "can", "win", "without", "Ohio", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"], "LOCATION": ["Ohio"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "General?", "question_tokens": ["General", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Thanks, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Thanks", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "The moment that happened on Monday night, did you think and assume that the race would get canceled?", "question_tokens": ["The", "moment", "that", "happened", "on", "Monday", "night", ",", "did", "you", "think", "and", "assume", "that", "the", "race", "would", "get", "canceled", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "I had to assume.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "to", "assume", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday"], "TIME": ["night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "When you heard that it was going ahead, what did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "heard", "that", "it", "was", "going", "ahead", ",", "what", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "I was actually a little bit shocked.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "actually", "a", "little", "bit", "shocked", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Well, I think it's probably the right decision, but it seems to be the wrong timing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "probably", "the", "right", "decision", ",", "but", "it", "seems", "to", "be", "the", "wrong", "timing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Michael, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Michael", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "I have no horse in this race.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "horse", "in", "this", "race", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Would Churchill have canceled the marathon?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "Churchill", "have", "canceled", "the", "marathon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "ORGAN: I think if the people of London, if we had had one of these --", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "I", "think", "if", "the", "people", "of", "London", ",", "if", "we", "had", "had", "one", "of", "these", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "Why has it been so belated, the help that you so desperately need?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "has", "it", "been", "so", "belated", ",", "the", "help", "that", "you", "so", "desperately", "need", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "RIMM: You know, I don't know exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["RIMM", ":", "You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "What is your reaction to Mayor Bloomberg canceling the marathon?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "Mayor", "Bloomberg", "canceling", "the", "marathon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Well, I think that the mayor did the right thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "the", "mayor", "did", "the", "right", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mayor Bloomberg"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Eastern Seaboard"], "LOCATION": ["Staten Island"]}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "And what reassurance can you give the people there now that they're getting your full attention?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "reassurance", "can", "you", "give", "the", "people", "there", "now", "that", "they", "'re", "getting", "your", "full", "attention", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Well, first, let me say that my heart goes out to the people on Staten Island and the people up and down the Eastern Seaboard.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", ",", "let", "me", "say", "that", "my", "heart", "goes", "out", "to", "the", "people", "on", "Staten", "Island", "and", "the", "people", "up", "and", "down", "the", "Eastern", "Seaboard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "If people are watching and wish to contribute to the Red Cross for this, what's the best way of doing that?", "question_tokens": ["If", "people", "are", "watching", "and", "wish", "to", "contribute", "to", "the", "Red", "Cross", "for", "this", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "best", "way", "of", "doing", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "They can visit our website, RedCross.org, or they can call 1-800-RED-CROSS.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "can", "visit", "our", "website", ",", "RedCross.org", ",", "or", "they", "can", "call", "1-800-RED-CROSS", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rudy Giuliani"]}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "What did you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Certainly Rudy Giuliani is a guy to be able to talk about this honestly.", "answer_tokens": ["Certainly", "Rudy", "Giuliani", "is", "a", "guy", "to", "be", "able", "to", "talk", "about", "this", "honestly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "I've got to stand right there with the people suffering?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "got", "to", "stand", "right", "there", "with", "the", "people", "suffering", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Michael Wolff, who is going to win this election?", "question_tokens": ["Michael", "Wolff", ",", "who", "is", "going", "to", "win", "this", "election", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Barack Obama.", "answer_tokens": ["Barack", "Obama", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Wolff"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121102pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Were you surprised by the sheer scale of the enthusiasm that Christie showed?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "surprised", "by", "the", "sheer", "scale", "of", "the", "enthusiasm", "that", "Christie", "showed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Totally.", "answer_tokens": ["Totally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]